here to help us understand the uh
complexities of this issue is our new
nightly show special commentator Susie
esman welcome Susie
Larry right
s great very well thanks Larry I mean
I've got one major problem with this new
libido drug why would a woman of my age
in God's name would I want my libido
back every dumb thing I ever did in my
youth was because I was listening to the
deranged little voice in my head telling
me I needed to get laid every hangover
every fake orgasm every time I broke
into Bill Pullman's house so I could
hide in his closet while he slept and
this was the '90s Bill Pullman just to
be clear one thing I don't need is my
cter doing Jedi Mind Tricks on Me Like
Obi vag
Kenobi
um you just said Obi vag Kenobi right
yes I did okay I just want to be clear I
just want to be clear now now there are
women who have low libido and miss
having sex that that's definitely a
thing maybe check out this quote from a
woman in the New York Times no less
replacing the dread I have for intimacy
with desire would be lifechanging I
would think so all I'm saying is if
you're literally dreading intimacy maybe
there's something else going on the
thing that gets me
is this assumption that just because you
don't want to have sex you have a mental
disorder hey fellas maybe your wife's
not crazy maybe she just doesn't want to
you good point I'm just saying a good
point have you tried hitting the gym
buying her flowers having sex that's not
just 45 seconds of jackhammering
followed by a sweaty
apology are the FG FDA rejected this
thing twice before and they might have
been right I mean listen to these side
effects this is a drug you take every
day and then go out and have your daily
routine so if you pass out while driving
a car if you pass out while you're
taking your kids to school and hit your
head I mean this can be serious and
unexpected a sex pill that might make
you pass
out which doctor is endorsing this
besides doctor
hustable hey solid
that was a solid Cosby Bird that's right
mother even our commentators haven't
forgotten about
you you beta and finally I just want to
say I know people think this is a
feminist issue like you said Larry sex
pills have been out there for men men
have 26 women have zero which by the way
is also most couples orgasm
ratio one of the groups fighting for
approval FDA approval is of this wonder
drug is called even the score all right
they've done a great job of framing this
in terms of orgasm equality but because
I have free time on my hand from all the
non- banging I do I found out that even
the score is just a PR campaign funded
by the drug company that makes this pill
it's like if your meth dealer tried to
tell you that you needed to buy his meth
because you suffer from having too many
teeth whole thing is just
spin um that's fascinating so it sounds
like this wasn't a win for science or
feminism but just for Branding and for
women who love to fall asleep while
they're driving oh that makes sense that
makes sense look maybe there's a great
female sex pill out there but I don't
know if this is it and besides I don't
want a pill that increases desire I want
a pill that increases
satisfaction that makes sense okay that
makes sense I
mean Hello makes sense for once I could
be the one orgasming after 45 seconds
then fall asleep and then he could be
the one poking me because I'm snoring so
loud makes sense enthusi assment
everyone